pornparco.com 2009-12-07

# Free Asian Porn, Japanese Porn, Free Amateur Porn, Homemade Sex Video, Adult XXX Video, Free Porn Online

| 
* **Privacy Statement**

Pornparco.com is committed to protecting your privacy. Pornparco.com does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies. Pornparco.com will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. The following contains details on how we treat all information collected on Pornparco.com. 

* **Personal Information**

**All Users Activity**

Any User can use Pornparco.com without having a account or any other Account. 

**Usage Information**

We may record information about your usage, such as when you use Pornparco.com, how many times you visit the website and other non-personal identifiable information. 

**Uses**

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through Pornparco.com, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of Pornparco.com, and to process any flagging activity or correspondence you send to us. 

\- We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Pornparco.com changes). 

\- We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of Pornparco.com and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications. 

\- We use cookies and log file information to: 

**1.** provide custom, personalized content and information.

**2.** monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

**3.** monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, time on site, bounce rate, etc... 

* **Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites**

Pornparco.com allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within Pornparco.com. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on Pornparco.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. Pornparco.com does not provide any personally identifiable information to third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.
